

## Vo Thi Cam Nhung

#### CONTACT INFORMATION -

- ☐ October 18, 1995
- □ Female
- 0983114763
- □ vothicamnhung1995@gmail.com
- ☐ Can Tho City

## OBJECTIVE

Hope to apply the experience in sales skills, products introduction as well as combining with specialized knowledge in 5 years with the skills and strengths of myself to become a good Medical Representative. And can bring more value to customers, connect between the company and customers. At the same time, I'm looking forward to learning more things in the professional, dynamic working environment of the multinational company to improve myself and accumulate much experience for future promote.

### SKILLS -

English skills and computer skills

Computer skills

Communication skills

Teamwork skills

Working under high pressure

Sales and introduce products

Planning skills, problem solving skills

Presentation, persuasion skills

## **EDUCATION** -

Oct 2013 - present

Can Tho University of Medicine and Pharmacy

Major: Pharmacy GPA: 8.65/10

Will graduate in June 2018

## WORK EXPERIENCE

May 2014 - March 2017

## Hoa Nong Lua Vang Company

### Seasonal sales staff

Main responsibilities:

- Introduce products and answer customers' queries.
- Synthesize opinions, needs, tastes of customers.
- Make sales report every day.

April 2017 - August 2017

## An Giang Plant Protection Joint Stock Company

Part-time Sales Staff

- Introduce products.

Achievements and skills gained:

- More active.
- Observe, learn and catch customers' taste well.
- Improve communication skill.

## ACTIVITIES —

November 2013 - February 2018

## **Dong Thap Students Association**

#### Core member

- Planning events every semester.

November 2013 - August 2017

## Youth Volunteer Team at university

#### Core member

- Planning events every month.

2014 - present

## Green Summer Volunteer Campaign

#### Volunteer

- Tutoring for disadvantaged children.

2014 - 2015

# Pharmacy Youth Union Executive Committe Member

- Management.
- Plan extra-curricular activities for Pharmacy students

Achievements and skills gained:

- Communication skill and Leadership.
- Learn how to organize social events.

## **INTERESTS**

Travelling

Joining in social activities

Singing, reading book

Playing chess and badminton

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

English Certificate level B

Computer Certificate level A

## **HONORS & AWARDS**

Received Excellent Student award for 4 consecutive years

Received Student of 5 merits award for 4 consecutive years

Received encouraging Scholarship in 9 consecutive semesters

## PERSONAL QUALITIES

- Sense of responsibility, carefulness in all the works done are my greatest strengths.
- Positive, motivated and hard- working person who is keep on working and contributing.
- Proactive to work in team or individually to complete all tasks given.